{
    "id": "1b9c936a46e945b58b7ed5225f1231aa",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise | Prepositions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We climbed ……………….. the hill with great difficulty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Distribute these toffees ...................... these two boys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Riches are a source ....................... great distress.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Cut your coat according ..................... your cloth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We should try to live ..................... our means.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "within",
                "with in",
                "beyond"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A man is known …………………. the company he keeps.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She was born ..................... noble parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The lion pounced ………………… the deer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This way, you can kill two birds ………………….. one stone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was killed ………………….. the robber ………………….. a sword.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by, by",
                "by, with",
                "with, with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}